<resources>
    <string name="app_name">HyTalkPTT</string>
    <string name="accessibility_description">HyTalk PTT Automation Service</string>
    <string name="ptt_setup_warn_accessibility_off">HyTalkPTT is OFF in Settings → Accessibility. Enable it for side/programmable PTT keys. If Bluetooth PTT still shows nothing below, your mic may use a non-standard protocol (e.g. SPP only) that Android does not expose as keys.</string>
    <string name="ptt_setup_instruction">Press the device side PTT key (shown here via keyboard events). Bluetooth: only works if the phone delivers headset or media keys to apps (HFP hook / AVRCP). Many dedicated PTT mics (e.g. some Inrico models) use a private protocol — then nothing appears in logcat (tag HyTalkPTT-MediaBtn) and you must use the device’s own PTT key only.</string>
    <string name="ptt_source_hardware">Device PTT key (programmable / side key)</string>
    <string name="ptt_source_bluetooth">Bluetooth headset / microphone PTT (HFP hook, AVRCP play/pause)</string>
    <string name="ptt_save_bluetooth_reminder">Important: enable “Bluetooth headset / microphone PTT” above and tap Save. Until you Save, headset keys are not registered when you leave this screen (see log: Bluetooth PTT OFF).</string>
    <string name="ptt_bluetooth_hint">Huawei often sends headset PLAY/PAUSE to com.android.mediacenter (Huawei Music), not to other apps — system log: “Sending KeyEvent … to com.android.mediacenter”. Force-stop or disable Huawei Music / Media center, enable Bluetooth PTT + Save, then try again. Dedicated PTT on some mics never appears in system logs — use the phone side key. Diagnose: adb logcat | grep -i MediaSessionService</string>
    <string name="ptt_bt_include_media_play">AVRCP Play (MEDIA_PLAY) triggers PTT — uncheck if the headset power / hook button falsely keys PTT (same key code as many “play” buttons).</string>
    <string name="ptt_save_need_source">Enable at least one PTT source</string>
    <string name="ptt_saved">Saved</string>
    <string name="main_configure_programmable_keys">Configure Programmable Keys (for Motorola)</string>
    <string name="main_setup_instructions">Scroll screen…\n\nOther accessibility services may interfere with global key capture. For reliable PTT, enable only HyTalkPTT under Settings → Accessibility (turn off any others you do not need).\n\nTo use HyTalkPTT, do this in order:\n\n1) Accessibility: tap Configure Accessibility — Settings → Accessibility → HyTalkPTT → enable the toggle\n2) Configure PTT Key: tap Configure PTT Key — press your PTT button, enable Bluetooth PTT if needed, then Save settings\n3) Configure Programmable Keys (for Motorola): Settings → Programmable Keys → Select PTT Key app → HyTalkPTT</string>
</resources>
